https://www.ihavenet.com/privacy.html

COMPANIES
3M (MMM)
AT&T (T)
AIG (AIG)
Alcoa (AA)
Altria (MO)
American Express (AXP)
Apple (AAPL)
Bank of America (BAC)
Boeing (BA)
Caterpillar (CAT)
Chevron (CVX)
Cisco (CSCO)
Citigroup (C)
Coca Cola (KO)
Dell (DELL)
DuPont (DD)
Eastman Kodak (EK)
ExxonMobil (XOM)
FedEx (FDX)
General Electric (GE)
General Motors (GM)
Google (GOOG)
Hewlett-Packard (HPQ)
Home Depot (HD)
Honeywell (HON)
IBM (IBM)
Intel (INTC)
Int'l Paper (IP)
JP Morgan Chase (JPM)
J & J (JNJ)
McDonalds (MCD)
Merck (MRK)
Microsoft (MSFT)
P & G (PG)
United Tech (UTX)
Wal-Mart (WMT)
Walt Disney (DIS)
RSS
Privacy Policy
iHaveNet.com (Promique.com, LLC) Privacy Policy
Welcome to iHaveNet.com (owned and produced by promiQue.com, LLC). iHaveNet.com is offered by promiQue.com, LLC
through www.ihavenet.com and is made available subject to this Privacy Policy.
By using this site, you agree,
without limitation or qualification, to be bound by this Privacy Policy.
Our policy may be updated from time to time so please check back periodically.
www.iHaveNet.com contains links to other sites, and while we are highly selective of the links we provide,
we cannot ensure, represent or guarantee their privacy policy.
Please, bear in mind
that the sites linked to from www.iHaveNet.com may have privacy policies that differ from those of
www.iHaveNet.com.
Information of yours collected by iHaveNet.com
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from www.ihavenet.com (the "Site").
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your
web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the
Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred
you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information
as "Device Information."
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
- "Cookies" are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information
about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit
www.allaboutcookies.org.
- "Log files" track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service
provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
- "Web beacons," "tags," and "pixels" are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
When we talk about "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information
Our site only collects anonymous information
Anonymous information refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual.
Each time a visitor comes to www.iHaveNet.com, we collect some information to improve the overall
quality of our visitors' online experience. We collect device information:
- IP addresses (e.g., whether the user is logged on from a .com, .gov or .edu domain);
- Referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL a user visited prior to clicking through to
www.iHavenet.com);
- Browser and platform type (e.g., a Netscape browser on a Windows platform).
Personally identifiable information refers to information that tells us specifically who you are,
such as your name, email address and/or mailing address.
We may collect personally identifiable information
under the following circumstance:
- If you contact us (phone, fax, mail and/or email), we may keep a record of that contact and correspondence.
We use the information provided so that we may respond to you via e-mail.
Sharing Your Personal Information
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.
We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site -- you can read more about how Google uses your
Personal Information here:
https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/.
You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:
https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
We may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena,
search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
Behavioural Advertising
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications
we believe may be of interest to you.
For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network
Advertising Initiative's ("NAI") educational page at
http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
NAI-approved Opt-Out mechanism for Interest-Based Advertising
http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance's opt-out portal at:
http://optout.aboutads.info/.
Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies
We use cookies and other similar technologies to help provide Services, to advertise to you and to analyse how you use our
Services and whether advertisements are being viewed. We also allow third parties to use tracking technologies for similar
purposes.
We use tracking technologies for the following purposes:
Performance purposes
To analyse how visitors use a website, for instance which pages visitors visit most often, in order to provide a better
user experience. We also use this technology to check if you have opened our emails, so we can see if they are being
delivered correctly and are of interest.
Personalisation purposes
To remember choices you have made -- such as language or region.
Advertising cookies
To limit the number of times you see an advertisement, or to customize advertising across Services and make it more relevant
to you and to allow us to measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns and track whether ads have been properly displayed
so we can pay for this.
Social media cookies
Cookies are used by social media services to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks.
These
cookies may track your browser across other sites and build a profile of your interests, which may impact the content and
messages you see on other websites that you visit.
How to manage & remove cookies
If you are using our Services via a browser you can restrict, block or remove cookies through your web browser settings.
The Help menu on the menu bar of most browsers also tells you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to
delete old cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie and how to disable cookies altogether.
You can also visit http://www.aboutcookies.org for more information
on how to manage and remove cookies across a number of different internet browsers.
You also have the option to change your
choices relating to cookies utilized to deliver behaviorally targeted advertising here "Advertising cookies".
Do Not Track
Please note that we do not alter our Site's data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
Your Rights
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your
personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through
the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts
we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business
interests listed above.
Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to
Canada and the United States.
Changes
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
Links to other sites
Be aware that iHaveNet.com has links that take you to other sites that may collect personally identifiable information
about you. We hope that all third parties involved adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our users.
However, this iHaveNet.com Privacy Policy does not cover third party data collection practices and
iHaveNet.com and promiQue.com, LLC do not assume any responsibility for any actions of third parties.
Contact Us
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please
contact us by e-mail at privacy @ promique.com.
WORLD NEWS & CURRENT EVENTS ...
WORLD NEWS & CURRENT EVENTS ...
Opinion: "Privacy Policy & Privacy Statement - iHaveNet.com"
